[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "EX", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VBG", "VBD", "VBG", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "Is there some surprise that he hasn't already taken action and fired those responsible?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "some", "surprise", "that", "he", "has", "n't", "already", "taken", "action", "and", "fired", "those", "responsible", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Well, it's a difficult situation over there because the alternative to not knowing was knowing which would have been another headache.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "difficult", "situation", "over", "there", "because", "the", "alternative", "to", "not", "knowing", "was", "knowing", "which", "would", "have", "been", "another", "headache", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "Mr. Mayor, what is your reaction to Chris Christie's statement late this afternoon?", "question_tokens": ["Mr.", "Mayor", ",", "what", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "Chris", "Christie", "'s", "statement", "late", "this", "afternoon", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "That he's appalled.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "he", "'s", "appalled", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Mayor", "Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "Do you believe that Chris Christie knew nothing about this as he claims?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "Chris", "Christie", "knew", "nothing", "about", "this", "as", "he", "claims", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "I don't know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "It's hard to imagine a more serious abuse of power, isn't it Mr. Mayor?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "hard", "to", "imagine", "a", "more", "serious", "abuse", "of", "power", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "Mr.", "Mayor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "I would agree, you know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "agree", ",", "you", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Mayor"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New Jersey"]}, "docId": "140108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "Should people be fired, should any of any of these people be in a job by tomorrow morning one to be name in shame today?", "question_tokens": ["Should", "people", "be", "fired", ",", "should", "any", "of", "any", "of", "these", "people", "be", "in", "a", "job", "by", "tomorrow", "morning", "one", "to", "be", "name", "in", "shame", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "NNS", "VB", "VBN", ",", "MD", "DT", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CD", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "OKOLICH: People that are in these positions of authority that behave this way, that put petty politics ahead of the health safety and welfare of my residents and the residents of the entire state of New Jersey truly can't be in those positions.", "answer_tokens": ["OKOLICH", ":", "People", "that", "are", "in", "these", "positions", "of", "authority", "that", "behave", "this", "way", ",", "that", "put", "petty", "politics", "ahead", "of", "the", "health", "safety", "and", "welfare", "of", "my", "residents", "and", "the", "residents", "of", "the", "entire", "state", "of", "New", "Jersey", "truly", "ca", "n't", "be", "in", "those", "positions", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "Have you heard from anybody in Chris Christie's camp including the governor's staff?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "heard", "from", "anybody", "in", "Chris", "Christie", "'s", "camp", "including", "the", "governor", "'s", "staff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "No, zero.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "zero", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "140108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "No apology?", "question_tokens": ["No", "apology", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Remain mindful, Piers, I'm not on his radar, so I trust, I'm not in his (inaudible) either.", "answer_tokens": ["Remain", "mindful", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "on", "his", "radar", ",", "so", "I", "trust", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "in", "his", "(", "inaudible", ")", "either", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "What is your reaction to this extraordinary development today which lays clear evidence now that takes right to the heart of Chris Christie's operation that they did this deliberately?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "this", "extraordinary", "development", "today", "which", "lays", "clear", "evidence", "now", "that", "takes", "right", "to", "the", "heart", "of", "Chris", "Christie", "'s", "operation", "that", "they", "did", "this", "deliberately", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "NNS", "VBP", "NN", "RB", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Well, I have been involved in this issue for four months which Mayor Sokolich knows.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "have", "been", "involved", "in", "this", "issue", "for", "four", "months", "which", "Mayor", "Sokolich", "knows", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "-- if I could jump in, should Chris Christie be firing people over this?", "question_tokens": ["--", "if", "I", "could", "jump", "in", ",", "should", "Chris", "Christie", "be", "firing", "people", "over", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", ",", "MD", "NNP", "NNP", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Is it likely that that was ever in their minds?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "likely", "that", "that", "was", "ever", "in", "their", "minds", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "Well, if you call the traffic study three or four days beforehand where you have the idea put forward that you're going to close a few lanes and look at that, I suppose you vaguely could call that a traffic study.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "you", "call", "the", "traffic", "study", "three", "or", "four", "days", "beforehand", "where", "you", "have", "the", "idea", "put", "forward", "that", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "close", "a", "few", "lanes", "and", "look", "at", "that", ",", "I", "suppose", "you", "vaguely", "could", "call", "that", "a", "traffic", "study", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["September"], "PERSON": ["John"]}, "docId": "140108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ":", "NN", ":", "CC", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "It was over 30 years that's been done that way, you know, why not continue?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "over", "30", "years", "that", "'s", "been", "done", "that", "way", ",", "you", "know", ",", "why", "not", "continue", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Yeah, as you're talking, John, we're actually looking pictures from the time back in September where you can see the traffic currents (ph) and everything else.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "as", "you", "'re", "talking", ",", "John", ",", "we", "'re", "actually", "looking", "pictures", "from", "the", "time", "back", "in", "September", "where", "you", "can", "see", "the", "traffic", "currents", "(", "ph", ")", "and", "everything", "else", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "How serious could this be for Chris Christie?", "question_tokens": ["How", "serious", "could", "this", "be", "for", "Chris", "Christie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "DT", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "It's very serious I think it could threaten his presidential ambitions if he is directly tied to this scandal which he hasn't yet been.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "very", "serious", "I", "think", "it", "could", "threaten", "his", "presidential", "ambitions", "if", "he", "is", "directly", "tied", "to", "this", "scandal", "which", "he", "has", "n't", "yet", "been", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 245, "question": "Do you like the fact that you have this slightly intimidating reputation?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "like", "the", "fact", "that", "you", "have", "this", "slightly", "intimidating", "reputation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 246, "answer": "I don't like or just like it, it's just kind of what it is.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "like", "or", "just", "like", "it", ",", "it", "'s", "just", "kind", "of", "what", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]